<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cost Manager</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Cost Manager</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Spend Less and Save More</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Expense</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Income</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Statistics</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tips</string>
    <string name="menu_calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Note</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Need Help?</string>
    <string name="longPressed1">to change this click Modify button.</string>
    <string name="longPressed2">to remove this click Delete button.</string>
    <string name="calculator">Simple Calculator</string>
    <string name="incomeText">If your want to set this month income click Monthly button.\nIf you want to add day by day income click Daily button</string>
    <string name="seven_simple_way"> <b><big>7 simple ways to save money</big></b>\n\n
        1)Record your expenses. The first step to start saving money is to figure out how much you spend.\n
        2)Budget for savings.\n
        3)Find ways you can cut your spending.\n
        4)Decide on your priorities.\n
        5)Pick the right tools.\n
        6)Make saving automatic.\n
        7)Watch your savings grow.</string>
    <string name="save_often"><b><big>Save Little And Often</big></b>\n\n
        It is a common mistake to think that you can not start saving because you do not have much money,
        but that is like saying you will not go on that one hour run because you do not have the whole day off to exercise – it is counterproductive and unrealistic.
        Experts advise that the best way to boost your bank balance is by taking the little and often approach to saving.
        Rather than putting a lump sum of your months wages into a savings account and leaving very little to live off for the rest of the month,
        just put a small amount away as often as possible and the money will mount up without you even noticing it.
        The more you see your bank balance rising, the more you will want to keep adding to it. Go on, try it – it is addictive.
    </string>

    <string name="get_support"> <b><big>Get Support</big></b>\n\n
        If you are really feeling the pinch and you need advice, do not feel ashamed to seek support from others.
        You may feel like a little fish in a big pond when it comes to finances,
        so seek advice from a financial expert who will have a lot of experience dealing with problems like yours.
        Your financial adviser will come up with a realistic plan to help you sort out any money difficulties.
        Perhaps even check for a free government run money advice service, rather then forking out for a private professional.
    </string>
    <string name="easy_steps">
         <b><big>Easy Tips to Save Money in Your Social Circle </big></b>\n\n\n
        People are social creatures. We tend to mirror those around us.
        So if you are trying to create your first budget, cut costs, earn more, or generally trying to trim unnecessary spending,
        you should take a long, hard look at the people around you.
        Tips to Save Money in Your Social CircleLike it or not, our social circle - colleagues, neighbors, friends,
        family - ​plays a huge role in shaping our attitudes and behaviors towards money.
        If you are concerned that the people in your life are not supporting your decision to live a more budget-conscious lifestyle,here are a few tips.\n\n
        Pick Who You Hang Out With Carefully\n\n
        You tend to imitate those around you.
        I am not saying you should completely give up spending time with your friends who are more carefree with their money.
        Income inequality can affect friendship in many ways, but, after all, friendship is priceless.
        However, for the time being, maybe you should focus on spending your Friday nights with the portion of your friends that tend to be more cost conscious.
        If all your friends are getting the VIP bottle service at a night club, you may be tempted to do so as well.
        If you hang out with that group of friends that would rather get a frozen pizza and watch Netflix, then you will most likely do the same.\n\n
        Suggest Cheaper Activities\n\n
        How can you spend time with those friends who like to spend? Be the person who suggests activities.
        Your friends might fall back on their standard habits of dining out at restaurants or hitting up bars if no one suggests an alternative.
        Taking it upon yourself to mention a different activity means you can pick something that is both fun and wallet-friendly.
        Going on a night hike, playing board games, playing soccer at the park, watching movies at home, or having a jam session in the living room are all great options.
        As an added bonus, you may become more popular with your friends because they will no longer have to come up with fun ideas or activities.
        You will naturally become the central organizer within your group of friends. Who knew pinching pennies could lead to stronger friendships?\n\n
        Get Your Spouse on Board (If You Have One)\n\n
        Nothing can decimate your budget faster than a spouse who does not share your vision or does not enjoy following through with the execution.
        By motivating your spouse, you will also motivate yourself. Sometimes the best way to stick to a plan is by enlisting the help of an accountability buddy.
        There is no one better than your spouse or partner to fill that role. You may even decide you need to keep money separate in your marriage.
        What should you do if your spouse is not interested? Ask him or her to create a vision board to discover the underlying "why," the motive,
        behind this new-found frugality.
        If they do not understand your desire to budget, they might after recognizing that you are skipping a restaurant tonight so that you can make a down payment on a house,
        or retire five years earlier than planned, or get rid of your car payments once and for all.
        You can explain that budgeting is not about depriving yourself of a few indulgences.
        It is about inching closer to your big goals.
        Skipping dessert does not feel like such a sacrifice when you realize the money you would have spent on chocolate cake is now extra money in your Aruba travel fund.
    </string>
    <string name="tricks_saving">
        <b><big>31 Money Saving Tricks for Students</big></b>\n\n\n
        1. Buy or rent used textbooks and sell last semester is books back.\n
        2. Do not make impulse purchases.\n
        3. Never go grocery shopping when you are hungry.\n
        4. Limit the number of times you eat out monthly.\n
        5. Cut out vices – smoking and binge drinking are terrible for you and expensive.\n
        6. Always pay bills on time to avoid late fees.\n
        7. If you have a credit card, pay it off as quickly as possible. (It is good to establish credit, but a bad credit score follows you everywhere.) \n
        8. Walk, use public transportation or ride a bike instead of having a car.\n
        9. Live with others so you can split rent and utilities.\n
        10. Cut out expensive cable packages you do not need.\n
        11. Consider more basic phone packages or plans that include unlimited texting with free incoming calls\n
        12. Do not buy the most expensive college meal plans. Figure out what you actually consume and get the correlating package.\n
        13. Shop where they offer student discounts. There are so many places that offer discounts to students with a school ID. \n
        14. Look into a campus gym versus a gym in town. Many colleges offer memberships for free or at a reduced rate for students.\n
        15. When planning meals, make dinner with friends and split the cost of groceries. Often times, you will be cooking too much for one person anyway!\n
        16. Sell what you no longer use or need. There are plenty of stores and web sites, like Poshmark and Craigslist,
        where you can sell your used clothing, furniture or tech items.\n
        17. Do not buy unnecessary school supplies. Why buy cumbersome notebooks when you can type on your laptop? It is better for the earth anyway!\n
        18. Do not buy books you will only need for a short period of time – check them out from the library instead.\n
        19. Take advantage of what your campus has to offer in terms of activities, rather than spending money on going out.
        Many campuses have an array of museums, offer movie nights and other social events for cheaper or, sometimes, for free.\n
        20. Skip expensive spring break and summer trips – look into alternatives, like volunteering, instead. \n
        21. Wait to get a pet until after college – a pet can become very expensive. Not only do you have another mouth to feed,
        but veterinary bills are costly. If you love animals, there are plenty of shelters that need volunteers.\n
        22. Go to class. You are paying for it and skipping is like throwing money out the window!\n
        23. Drink water. It is free and better for you, anyway.\n
        24. Make your own coffee. While coffee shops are convenient, they charge hefty prices that really add up over time.\n
        25. Open a savings account that earns interest. Credit unions have fewer fees and are great for students.\n
        26. Use a free tool, like FinAids Student Budget Calculator or the one offered by Mint.com, to keep track of your finances.
        It is harder to be frivolous when you see where your money is going.\n
        27. Never take out a loan for anything that is unrelated to your education. \n
        28. Do not buy music. Use the free services like Spotify or Pandora offer.\n
        29. Look into class requirements and the options for testing out of classes. Why pay for a class you could easily test out of?\n
        30. Consider becoming a resident advisor. Many get free room and board.\n
        31. Avoid buying name brand items. Purchase generic items whenever possible. They are exactly the same item, at a highly reduced price.
        You can even check the ingredients to make sure!\n
    </string>
    <string name="need_help"><b><big>How to add Expense</big></b>\n\n
        To add expense click the button that has plus icon(+) at the bottom in maun menu.
        Then it will show a new window where you can add or save your expense\n\n
        <b><big>How to Delete or Modify daily expense data?</big></b>\n\n

If you want to delete or modify your data, go to your “Daily Expense” then long press the desire data from the list .
 A Popup window will show two option for delete or modify. If you click delete button then data will be deleted.
If you click the modify button then another window will let you modify data as you want.\n\n

<b><big>How to Delete or Modify Monthly expense data?</big></b>\n\n

If you want to delete or modify your data, go to your “Monthly Expense” then long press the desire data from the list .
 A Popup window will show two option for delete or modify. If you click delete button then data will be deleted.
If you click the modify button then another window will let you modify data as you want.\n\n

<b><big>How to Delete or Modify Yearly expense data?</big></b>\n\n

If you want to delete or modify your data, go to your “Yearly Expense” then long press the desire data from the list .
 A Popup window will show two option for delete or modify. If you click delete button then data will be deleted.
If you click the modify button then another window will let you modify data as you want.\n\n

<b><big>How to save Daily Income?</big></b>\n\n

Goto income, here you can add daily income by clicking Daily button.
 If your earning is daily wise then you enter you amount and click daily button then the amount will add with your previous daily income.
If you found any problem then clear all amount and then add daily wise amount\n\n

<b><big>How to save Monthly Income?</big></b>\n\n

Goto income, here you can set monthly income by clicking Monthly button.
 If your earning is monthly wise then you enter you amount and click Monthly button then the amount will add as your monthly income.
If you found any problem then clear all amount and then add monthly wise income\n\n\n


<b><big>If you can not find your solution you can mail us.</big></b>\n\n
Email : <b><big>mdraihan7007@gamil.com</big></b>\n\n\n
    </string>


</resources>
